

IIII' Megan N. Reed

PERSONAL STATEMENT

On a mission to conceptualize, design, deliver and integrate user-driven digital experiences with insight into the nuances of the users/guests that are unique to the hospitality industry.

10+ years of experience across the spectrum of **Digital Design**, **UX & Marketing** with multi-cultural teams and high-growth companies **around the world**.

Advocate of the user. Designer of digital experiences & interfaces. Orchestrator & Partner at the intersection of high-tech & high-touch.

PROJECTS & TOOLSET

UpStay, Mobile App Design & Website

Digital product designed for on-demand booking of hotel services, managing the entire design cycle.

Selected Tools Used in Project:

- Ideation & Conceptual Design
- Information Architecture
- Rapid Wireframing & Prototyping
- Mobile App UI Design
- GitHub Collaboration
- Front-End Dev: HTML & CSS
- InVision Clickable Prototype

EveryBell, Website & Brand Identity

Hotel service product designed to make luxury hospitality accessible to rentals and residences.

Selected Tools Used in Project:

- User Stories & Personas
- Brand Strategy & Identity
- User Centered Design Methodology
- Content Creation
- Sketch App Design
- Adobe Illustrator Logo Design
- Hospitality Trend Analysis

myStamford, Web App & Website

Web application communication platform designed and developed with user-centered design methodology.

Selected Tools Used in Project:

- UX Research & Strategy
- User Surveys & Interviews
- Creative Direction
- Content Management
- Usability Testing (1:1 & Remote)

WORK EXPERIENCE

MIAMI, USA HEAD OF EXPERIENCE DESIGN

EVERYBELL | 2014 - Current

- Utilized a user-centered design methodology to lead UX and visual design across all channels including digital & non-digital for innovative service product.
- Conceptualized, designed, and owned brand strategy/identity; setting up design
 patterns to ensure consistency across all channels and product family.
- Led user research, product idea generation, conceptual wireframing and prototyping; executing design deliverables and ensuring operational standards.
- Communicated and facilitated executive level presentations; securing key
 partnership with hotel brand resulting in increased engagement and awareness.
- Executed email marketing campaigns with special focus on optimization, content creation, and analytics to effectively measure and focus on high-impact activities.

SINGAPORE SENIOR MANAGER, MARKETING & PRODUCT

STAMFORD | 2013 - 2014

- Creative direction from concept to launch for new digital and print brand marketing campaign resulting in 600% growth year-over year.
- Managed entire UX design cycle for new user-driven digital product design, driving an increase in client engagement and retention of 65% after launch.
- Set product vision and led onsite and remote team of designers and developers to redesign website and optimize for social media, analytics, and SEO.
- Planned, promoted, executed high-profile event drawing \$250K in media value.

SINGAPORE & GERMANY

CORPORATE MARKET MANAGER, APAC

HRS HOTEL PORTAL | 2011 - 2013

- Led multi-national team to secure valuable corporate partnerships in the region to achieve successful corporate expansion from Germany to APAC.
- Increased hotel bookings by 40% in the region through generating corporate client agreements of up to \$2M of revenue per campaign.
- Partnered with technology and product management to improve functionality of training platform for on-boarding of B2B clients through ensuring usability and understanding dependencies on other internal apps.
- Facilitated redesign and creative development of executive level presentations for hotel and corporate acquisition; securing key partnerships with major hotel brands.

HAWAII, USA GUEST EXPERIENCE LEAD

FOUR SEASONS HOTELS | 2009 - 2010

- Provided Executive committee with guest experience recommendations and insights for \$1M concept redesign for fine-dining restaurant.
- Collaborated to deliver menu and product design deliverables for new concept;
 recognized as #1 Big Island Restaurant and #1 Fine Dining Restaurant in Hawaii.
- Facilitated high-value guest experience interaction to inform insights for service standards and improve feedback and overall outlet rankings.
- Strategized promotional events to drive traffic, brand awareness and loyalty.

HAWAII, USA DENVER, USA

RECRUITMENT & OPERATIONS LEAD
TERRITORY MARKETING REPRESENTATIVE

YWAM | 2007 - 2009 INTUIT | 2006

EDUCATION

UX/UI DESIGN & FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT B.S. BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION, MARKETING

Bloc.io San Fransisco/Remote | 2016 - 2017 CCU Denver | 2002 - 2006